

PERSONAL

- Name
 Abhishek Mehta
- ★ Address
 5, Satyam Bungalows, Nr.
 Samarpan BRTS bus stand, Bopal,
 Ahmedabad 380058.
 380058 Ahmedabad
- Phone number 9974947228
- Email mehta7524@gmail.com
- Date of birth
 10-03-1994
- Place of birth Mumbai
- Male

 Mationality

Gender

- Indian

 Marital status
- Single

 LinkedIn

 https://www.linkedin.com/in/abhis
 mehta-2098a0101

INTERESTS

- Cycling
- Reading novels

ABHISHEK MEHTA

Skilled Automobile Engineer with over 8 years of experience in Automotive Technology, Quality Inspection & Maintenance. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction. To be a successful Quality Head in a reputed organisation.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2017 - Present

Certified Maintenance Technician

Central Star India Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

- Served as Certified Maintenance Technician & carried out Periodic Maintenance.
- Served as a Body Shop technician & Final Inspector.
- Vehicle dispatch tracking from Mercedes-Benz India Pvt. Ltd. & receiving at stockyard.
- Stock maintenance & periodic inspection every 14 days as per VPC check sheet.
- VPC stock audits & solve technical problems beforehand of delivery.
- **Perform Pre-delivery Inspection** for new, demo & Pre-owned vehicles with 82 point VPC check sheet.
- Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.

Aug 2016 - Feb 2017

Final Inspector

Atul Motors Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

- Check vehicle for complete analysis on work performed as per Job card.
- Improved quality assurance procedures to minimize errors and increase effectiveness of inspections.
- Prepared reports detailing findings of inspections, investigations, and tests.
- Handled & lead a team of 23 members in after-sales department.

Jan 2016 - May 2016

Supply Chain Supervisor

Prowiz Mansystems Limited - Tata Motors Sanand Plant, Ahmedabad

- Receiving production materials & stock with proper manpower distribution as per requirement in shifts.
- Maintain zero line stoppage & time management Worked flexible hours; night, weekend, and holiday shifts.
- Collaborated with Production and Purchase departments to facilitate smooth accomplishment of deadlines.
- Kept stock areas tidy & organised as per Kaizen & 5S rules.

Sep 2013 - Dec 2015

Quality Incharge

Parklane Cars Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

- Vehicle washing & work quality check beforehand delivery to customer.
- Overall visual inspection & vehicle road test post service work.
- Customer's voice analysis & provide satisfactory work followed by specified FRT.
- Completed precise measurements using special tools.
- Monitored performance and generated reports detailing service quality and customer satisfaction.

Apr 2013 - Sep 2013

Customer Service Advisor

Innovative Honda Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

- Greeting customer for vehicle service acceptance & understand his concern for schedule service.
- Service cost estimate discussion with customer followed by approval.
- Service Repair & Workshop Order preparation & check updates for work

process as per FRT.

- Communication to customer for additional repair cost thereby increase dealer business.
- Thorough assurance of vehicle service quality & customer satisfaction.
- Vehicle handover & accounting.
- Post service feedback calls.

May 2013 - Jun 2013 Trainee Engineer

Manan Autolink Pvt. Ltd., Ahmedabad

- Served as a trainee engineer with Maruti Suzuki Authorized Dealer.
- Perform general maintenance on vehicles under Senior Technician's guidance.
- Performed service & overhauling of minor engine assembly parts.
- Performed wheel alignment & wheel balancing as a part of service procedure.

Worked as a fresher for 3 months so no official paper offered by company.



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

May 2009 - May 2012 Diploma Automobile Engineering

L.J. INSTITUTE OF POLYTECHNIC, Ahmedabad

Passed with 8.4 C.G.P.A. and 9.1 S.P.I in last semester under Gujarat Technological University, Gujarat.

May 2008 - May 2009 S.S.C.

SHREE NARAYANA GURU VIDHYALAYA, Ahmedabad

Passed 10th Board examination with 50.31% under GSEB, Gujarat.



SKILLS

Active Work Performance

Quality Assurance / Control

Team Management

Decision Making

Microsoft word



ACHIEVEMENTS

- Certified Maintenance Technician from Mercedes-Benz India Limited 1 month OJT in March, 2018.
- Participated in Beardothon Running Marathon for 5kms in October, 2018.
- Gold Medalist in Automobile Development Internship (ADI), Organised by Ezenith Education in April, 2016.
- Winner of Bournvita Quiz Contest held during academics in February, 2002.